CHRISTIAN BRAGADO

FULL STACK ENGINEER

Los Angeles. CA (805) 338-2224

CHRISTIAN.BRAGADO@ICLOUD.COM

GIT**H**UB LINKEDIN

SUMMARY

Full-Stack software engineer proficient in using Javascript for front-end and back-end programming, React, HTML, CSS, API implementing, Node.JS, Express, PostgreSQL, and frameworks like Bootstrap. Bringing 10 years of work experience in the customer service and tech industry to utilize a strong understanding of teamwork, communication, and efficient problem-solving.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, jQuery

Backend: Node.js, Express, RESTful APIs, PostgreSQL

Tools: Mocha, Chai, Knex, Git, GitHub, Heroku, Node Package Manager, Visual Studio Code

PROJECTS

JavaScript, HTML5, Node.js, Bootstrap, Mocha, Chai. - Encryption Application | Thinkful | Github

- Assembled the functionality for an application that allows users to search, review and check out books from their local neighborhood.
- Created search and sorting functions to allow users to know what books were available and their ratings.
- Coded using JavaScript functions that are built to enable the expansion of the library with little to no need for code refactoring.
- Technology: JavaScript ES6, Bootstrap, HTML5, Node.js

JavaScript, React, Express, HTML, CSS, Git - Flash Card Application | Thinkful | Github

03/2022

- Created an application that allows users to create, edit, and delete decks and cards within them.
- Created a REST API and middleware functions to allow user(s) to create, read, update and delete their perfect deck of study cards.
- Defined routes and URLs, and used state over multiple components.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Apple Inc.

Los Angeles, CA

01/2018 - Present

- **Senior Technician** Delivered Level II and Level III technical support with a focus on the customer experience bringing a less
 - than 5% Same Unit Repair. Strategically addressed customer needs with deep knowledge of products and services consistently delivering an NPS score of 80+
 - Established a timeline with a protocol for harder-to-solve problems and effectively utilized technical resources for problem resolution which allowed me to deliver solutions averaging under 12 minutes, exceeding market team KPIs
 - Identified novel technical issues by replicating, documenting, and collaborating with engineers.
 - Isolated and classified issues for clear and concise documentation i.e. hardware, software, environmental issues.

Apple Inc.

Los Angeles, CA 01/2014 - 01/2018

Technical Specialist

- Developed a relationship with our customers while providing quick and efficient technical support.
- Identified customer's technical issues to provide a solution or escalated to other support team members.
- Provided swift yet effective training to our customers, helped them build confidence in their product.

EDUCATION

Thinkful Online

Certificate, [Engineering Immersion Program]

02/2022 - 07/2022

- Learned industry best practices and software development standards with a focus on Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, React Native, Node.js, PostgreSQL, RESTful APIs, algorithms, and data structures.
- Developed and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks, spending several hours per week collaborating with and learning from senior web developers in a mentor-student relationship

Moorpark College
Associate of Arts

Moorpark, CA **06/01/2019**